老爸老妈罗曼史\n第一季 第二十一集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 01 Episode 21
孩子们，人生就像一条黑暗的道路
Kids,life is a dark road.
你永远看不清前方等待你的将是什么
You never really know what's up ahead.
一个夜晚，当你独自享受的行驶在这条道路上时
One night you're cruising along enjoying the ride,
突然间
and then all of a sudden,
你28岁了
you're 28.
这是给生日男孩的千层面
For the birthday boy,lasagna.
谢谢
Thank you.
小心，盘子很烫
Careful.The plate is very hot.
好的
OKay.
哦，来吧，碰一下
Oh,go on,touch it.
见鬼
Sweet damn,
好烫的盘子
that's a hot plate.
好吧,那么,Barney,
All right,so,Barney,
你干不干啊?
are you doing this or what?
老天,Barney,别
jeez,Barney,don't do this.
我必须做，这是我给Ted的生日礼物
I have to,it's my birthday present to Ted.
你不是一定要做
You don't have to.
拜托，会很丢人的
Please,it's going to be embarrassing
我们以后都不敢再来了
and we're going to have to stop coming here,
这可不怎么好...
which will suck...
补充一点，不来这可能会更健康
in addition to probably being kind of healthy.
拜托,Marshall,
Come on,Marshall,
这在什么时候都是泡妞的好招
it's the greatest pickup line of all time.
Barney\nBarney.
天啊
gevalt.
生日快乐,Ted
happy birthday,Ted.
请原谅,有人告诉过你...
excuse me,has anyone ever told Y...
哦，天啊
oh,my god.
怎么?
What?
叫救护车!
Call an ambulance!
怎么回事?
What's going on?
别说话
Try not to speak.
来，坐下
Here,sit down.
只要别说话
Just don't talk,
别说话
don't talk.
她没事吧?
Is she okay?
我认真的,拨911
I'm serious,call 911.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
怎么回事?
What's the matter?
不要动
Just don't move.
Don't move.
只要试着...
Just try...
来，喝点水
here,have some water.
水!
Water!
来，喝了这个
Here,drink this.
你知道吗，我看得越多
You know,the more I watch this,
就越觉得这个任何时候都合适的泡妞妙招没什么说服力
the less convinced I am that it's the\ngreatest pickup line of all time.
等等
Wait for it.
28\n28.
还有两年就是重要的三十岁
Two more 'til the big one,three-O.
事实上，我的30岁生日也不太糟糕
Actually,my 30th birthday wasn't so bad.
除了我的洗手间多了只羊
except for the goat in my bathroom.
倒是个好故事
Which is a great story.
但我以后再讲
But I'll get to that later.
而且，你知道
Still,you know,
又老了一岁
another year older.
却还是单身
Still single.
你难道没有听到自己“Ted钟”在向前走吗?
You don't hear your Tedological clock ticking?
没有
Nope.
我按下睡眠键了
I hit the snooze button.
护理员来了
And here come the paramedics.
哦，谢天谢地，你们来了
Oh,thank god,you're here.
什么情况?!
What is going on?!
我想可能是内出血
I think there might be some internal bleeding.
可能有破裂
Probably some fractures.
我们必须送她去医院
We got to get her to the hospital.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你摔的很重
You've had a terrible fall.
我没有摔啊
No,I haven't.
真的吗?
Really?
我发誓你是从天堂摔落下的
Cause I could swear you fell straight out of heaven.
天使...
Angel...
给他你的号码
Give him your number.
什么?
What?
给他你的号码
Give him your number.
什么?
What?
给他你的号码
Give him your number.
你在让我难堪
you're embarrassing me.
给他你的号码
Give him your number.
你怎么...?
What are you...?
-来吧\n-给他你的号码
-Come on.\n-Give him your number.
你不给我号码
They're not going to stop
他们是不会停下的
'til you give me your number.
给他你的号码
Give him your number.
好吧!
All right!
成功!
It works!
我不敢相信她给了他号码
I cannot believe that she gave him her number.
她可能真的脑子受损了
Maybe she really does have a brain injury.
谢谢大家
Thank you,everyone.
这很有意思
It's been fun.
这是服务生Wendy
It's Wendy the waitress.
多给她点小费
Tip her well.
多谢你们
Thanks a lot,guys.
Troilus和Cressida
Troilus and Cressida.
来自隔壁的剧场
Neighborhood playhouse.
去看他们的表演吧，他们很不错
Check them out,they're good.
我知道我为什么还单身了
I realize why I'm still single.
我太挑剔了
I'm picky.
我不会定下来的
I'm not going to settle.
我要娶的人,
If I'm going to marry someone,
必须是完美的
she has to be perfect.
嗯，怎么样的完美?
Well,what's perfect?
具体我可不知道
It's not like I have a list.
哦，你知道
Oh,yes,you do.
迷人，大学毕业
Attractive,college-educated,
她想要两个孩子--
she wants two kids--
一个男孩，一个女孩...
a boy and a girl...
这不难
that's not hard.
-我知道，至少...\n-我还没说完
-I know at least...\n-I'm not done.
她喜欢狗
She likes dogs,
喜欢Otis Redding
Otis Redding,
喜欢做填字游戏
does the crossword.
擅长运动
She's into sports,
但是不要运动太多
but not so much so that her legs are,like,
腿上肌肉比我还多的那种
more muscular than mine.
我觉得太奇怪，不喜欢
That weirds me out.
而且她要能像Pixies里的Kim Deal\n那样弹低音电吉他
And she plays bass guitar like Kim \nDeal from the Pixies.
或者像Sonic Youth里的Kim Gordon
Or Kim Gordon from Sonic Youth.
或者像任何一个酷乐队里的Kim
Any Kim from any cool band,really.
不要太挑剔
Can't be too picky.
你永远找不到这样的女孩的
You're never going to find this girl.
完全正确
Exactly.
所以我只能等她来找我
So I'm just going to wait for her to come to me.
我不想再计划无法计划的事情了
I am done trying to plan the unplannable.
那么，你是认为命运会帮你搞定?
So,what,you think fate's just gonna take care of it?
这就是我的计划
That's the plan.
然而我不知道
And little did I know,
就在那一刻
at that very moment,
命运--
fate--
借助一台60万兆赫的超处理电脑
in the form of a 600 gigahertz superprocessing computer
帮我搞定了
was taking care of it.
你起早了
you're up early.
我还以为我要用烤薄饼这招呢
thought I'd whip up some pancakes.
Marshall知道吗?
Does Marshall know?
他听起来好像还在睡
He's still sound asleep.
太棒了
Awesome.
真太棒了
So awesome.
天! 你是最棒的女孩
God! Best girl ever.
干掉这些薄饼
Screw these pancakes,
我要用糖浆把你裹起来然后吞掉
I should cover you in syrup and gobble you up.
求你别那么做
Please don't do that.
嘿，牛奶没坏吧?
Hey,is this milk any good?
我昨天喝了，也这样
that totally got me yesterday.
天，那你为什么不扔掉?
God,why didn't you throw it away?
下班以后我要去买东西
I'm going shopping after work.
会带牛奶回来
I'll pick up some milk.
这些薄饼真让人高兴
These pancakes are delightful.
怎么回事，宝贝?
What's wrong,baby?
这是我一天中最快乐的时候
This is the high point of my day.
确实如此
It was true.
瞧,Marshall一直梦想能用自己的律师学位
See,Marshall had always dreamed\n of using his law degree
保护环境
to protect the environment.
但是他结婚需要钱
But he needed money for the wedding,
所以他在Barney的公司实习两个月了...
so he'd been interning for two months\n at Barney's firm...
他恨在那的每一分钟
and he hated every minute of it.
嘿,Barney,
Hey,Barney,
我填这些请购单时有点问题
I had some questions about filling\nout these requisition forms.
拿望远镜
Binoculars.
我桌上那副
Second pair on my desk.
我没时间玩匍匐的游戏,伙计
I don't have time to be creepy,dude.
我有很多事做
I have a lot of work to do.
就看一下，好吗?
Just take a look,will ya?
好
Okay,
角落的办公室
corner office.
最顶层
Top floor.
看这人
Check out that guy.
他叫Clark Butterfield
Name's Clark Butterfield.
他在“Nicholson,Hewitt与West”工作
He works over at Nicholson,Hewitt and West
每天早上,
and every morning,
他都要在楼下的熟食店定一个三明治
he orders a sandwich from the deli downstairs.
然后?
So?
猜猜我对他的三明治做了什么?
So guess what I did to that sandwich?
瞧，我拍了照
Here,I took a picture.
天啊
Sweet lord.
现在我要把这个照片发电子邮件给他
And now I'm e-mailing said picture to him.
蹲下!
Duck!
你有病啊!
That is sick!
为什么这么做?
Why would you do that?
谁知道?
Who knows?
这场交锋已经持续很久了
This feud goes so far back
我都记不得谁先开的火了
I can't remember who fired the first shot.
你?
You?
正确
Totally.
瞧，只要你...
look,if you would just...
你能帮我填完表格
help me fill out these forms,
就太棒了
that would be great.
什么?
What?
Butterfield会在四小时之内报复
Butterfield is going to retaliate\nwithin the next four hours.
这是他的模式
That's been his pattern.
现在是打仗,Eriksen
This is war,Eriksen.
我需要你改变日程,
I need you to clear your schedule,
打电话给Lily,告诉她你要晚下班
call Lily,tell her you'll be home late.
这太蠢了
This is stupid.
蠢...
Stu...
拜托，伙计,
come on,man,
我不是招你来这发挥你的律师技能的
I didn't recruit you to work\nhere for your lawyering skills.
我招你来是做我的恶作剧处理顾问
I recruited you to be my executive \nmischief consultant.
这是我的工作,Barney
This is a job for me,Barney.
是为婚礼多挣点钱的方法
It's a way to make some extra wedding money,
就这样
and that's it.
现在对不起
Now I'm sorry,
我还有工作要做
but I have work to do.
Tracy,请你进来一下好吗?
Tracy,could you come in here,please?
请你通知Eriksen先生
Would you please inform Mr. Eriksen
我再不会对他说话了
that I'm no longer speaking to him.
Eriksen先生,Stinson先生再不...
Mr. Eriksen,Mr. Stinson is no longer...
我听到了\n谢谢你,Tracy
I get it.Thank you,Tracy.
喂?
hello?
喂
Hello.
请找一下Ted Mosby先生?
May I speak with a Mr. Ted Mosby?
请讲
Speaking.
Mosby先生,你好吗?
Mr. Mosby,how you doing,sir?
我是爱情中心的Bob Rorschach
Bob Rorschach over here at love solutions.
六个月前，你曾申请过服务
You signed up for our services\n about six months ago.
你们永远都找不到合适我的人选
You guys never found me a match.
对
Right.
事实上，这就是我打来的原因
actually,that's why I'm calling.
我们找到她了，先生
We found her,sir.
我们找到和你天生一对的女孩了
We found your soul mate.
我不明白
I don't understand.
Ellen Pierce怎么不在?
what happened to Ellen Pierce?
她不是这的老板吗?
Doesn't she run this place?
我的公司买下了这里
my firm bought out the company.
你知道，我们是经营肉类和纺织品聚合的
You know,we're a high-end meats\nand textiles conglomerate,
但是，董事会的天才想让经营多样化...
but the geniuses at corporate decided\nthey wanted to diversify,so...
所以我来了
here I am.
这么说我找到可以高手了
So I'm in good hands.
你给我找到了合适的对象?
You found me a match?
她在这
There she is.
和你天生一对的女孩
Your soul mate.
这要收500美元
That'll be 500 bucks.
不行
No way.
上次我付了钱
The last time I did this,
那女孩却是订了婚的
the girl turned out to be engaged.
她没有订婚
She's not engaged.
她是和你天生一对的女孩
She's your soul mate.
看下文件吧
Just read the file.
于是我读了文件
so I read the file.
天啊
And by god,
这个女人很完美
this woman was perfect.
她喜欢狗
She liked dogs,
她在加州北部过夏天
she spent her summers in North Carolina,
她弹低音电吉他
she played bass guitar,
她做计时填字游戏
she did the times crossword,
她打网球
she played tennis,
她喜欢老电影
she liked old movies,
她最喜欢的食物是千层面
her favorite food was lasagna,
她最喜欢的书是“霍乱时期的爱情”
her favorite book was love in the time of cholera,
她最喜欢的歌手是Otis Redding
her favorite singer was Otis Redding
而且她想要两个孩子--
and she wanted two kids--
一个男孩和一个女孩
a boy and a girl.
好吧
All right,fine.
帮我安排吧
Set it up.
你想见我
You wanted to see me,
所以我猜这代表我们又讲话了?
so I guess that means we're talking again?
你能帮我尝尝这杯拿铁吗?
Will you taste this latte for me?
我想他们给了我无咖啡因的
I think they gave me decaf.
我觉得味道正常
Tastes normal to me.
我也这么想的
That's what I thought,too.
但是我收到了Butterfield的邮件
Then I got this e-mail from Butterfield.
天!
god!
我也受害了
It got me as well.
那你为什么还让我喝?!
then why did you have me drink it?!
因为现在...
Because now...
你要加入了
you're in.
好
Okay.
不要以为我会忽略
Don't think I'm overlooking the obvious fact
我应该生你的气这么明显的事实
that I should just be mad at you.
但是恶作剧处理顾问Marshall Eriksen要汇报今天的指责了
But executive mischief consultant\nMarshall Eriksen reporting for duty.
我们要让那个混蛋付出代价
Let's make that bastard pay.
我们应该先刷刷牙吧?
You think that we should brush our teeth first?
好像是个好主意
it's probably a good idea.
那一夜我与我完美的对象有个约会
So that night I had a blind date with my perfect match.
我太激动了
I was so excited,
所以去早了
I got there early.
但是在约会还没开始前...
But before it even started...
Lily?\nLily?
嘿,Ted,你忙吗?
Hey,Ted,are you busy?
是的
yes.
对了，天生一对，我忘了
right. Soul mate.Forgot.
听着你能坐出租车过来Duchess郡
Listen,could you take a cab out to Duchess county
来帮Marshall的Fiero车换个轮胎吗?
and change a flat on Marshall's Fiero?
什么?
What?
不
No.
你不能叫Marshall去吗?
Can't you just call Marshall?
Marshall不能知道这件事
Marshall can't know about this.
瞧,Ted,天黑了
Look,Ted,it's dark,
我不会换轮胎
I don't know how to change a tire,
而且我开始想一个很恐怖的野营故事了
and I've stumbled into the beginning\nof a very scary campfire story.
求你了
Can you please hurry?
我不行，我在等...
I can't,I'm waiting...
哦，我的天,那是一个带有一只铁钩手的流浪汉吗?
oh,my god,is that a drifter with a\nhook for a hand?
不，流浪汉，别!
No,drifter,no!
拜托,Lily
Come on,Lily.
你明白我意思了
But you see my point.
好吧，呆在那
all right,stay there.
我来了
I'm on my way.
于是
And so,
付了90美元出租车费后
one $90 cab ride later,
我到了个不知名的地方
I was in the middle of nowhere.
谢天谢地
thank god.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry about this.
你的约会推迟了吗?
Did you get a hold of your date?
对
Yes.
她对推迟一下没有意见吧?
And was she okay about pushing it back?
没有，因为她是完美的
Yes.Because she's perfect.
那么我为什么要来?
So what am I doing here?
你永远别告诉Marshall
You can never tell Marshall.
我不会的
I won't.
永远
Ever.
发誓
Swear.
用你没出生的儿子和女儿的生命发誓
Swear on the lives of your unborn boy and girl.
我用Luke和Leia发誓
I swear on Luke and Leia.
大概一个月前
About a month ago,
我开始失眠
I started getting insomnia.
我一直都很想嫁给Marshall
Marrying Marshall had been\nall I wanted for a long time.
但是，现在真的要发生了
But,now that it was really happening,
却好像太重大太可怕
it seemed kind of huge and scary.
你和Marshall谈过这事吗?
Did you talk to Marshall about it?
他不会懂的
He wouldn't have understood.
他对结婚不怎么紧张
He's not exactly nervous about tying the knot.
所以我晚上就读书
so I spent my nights reading,
画画
painting,
玩游戏，还得了最高分...
setting the high score on Super Bomberman...
是你?
That was you?
太棒了!
Awesome!
我知道!
I know!
我刚进入地带，...
I just got in the zone and...
这不是重点
not the point of the story.
然后我想到了Victoria
And then I started thinking about Victoria
她为了自己的梦想去了德国
and how she followed her dream to Germany,
然后我看到了这个艺术奖学金
then I found this art fellowship,
我猜猜
Let me guess.
在很远的地方
It's somewhere far away.
旧金山
San Francisco.
但是我不是要去做
But it's not like I'm going to do it.
日期和婚礼有冲突
The dates conflict with the wedding.
但我喜欢画画
But I love painting,
一直想知道自己画的好不好
and I've always wondered if I'm any good.
用这个方法可以找出答案
This was a way to find out.
面试是今晚
And the interview is tonight.
在New Haven
In New Haven.
你不想结婚
You don't want to get married.
我当然想结婚
Of course I want to get married.
我...
I...
不是说我一定会去
it's not like I was ever gonna do it.
我只是...
I just...
我只是想知道我能不能得到这个机会
I just really wanted to see if I could get this.
Lily,我们住在美国文化和艺术的中心
Lily,we live in the center of art and\n culture in America.
我确定你一定能在这找到一样有选择性的项目
I'm sure you could find a program here\nthat's just as selective.
但是你选择了3,000里以外的
But you chose one in a city 3,000 miles away,
而且你没有告诉Marshall
and you didn't tell Marshall.
我觉得这代表了什么已经很明显了
I think it's pretty clear what that means.
好吧，我...
Okay,I was...
我是动摇了
I was having second thoughts.
但我不会再了
But I'm not any more.
我...
I...
我的意思是，轮胎坏了就预示
I mean,this flat tire was a sign.
我不该这么做
I'm not supposed to do this.
我应该回家
I'm supposed to go home
和Marshall在一起
and-and be with Marshall.
你一定觉得我很傻
You must think I'm so stupid.
我不觉得你傻
I don't think you're stupid.
我爱Marshall
I love Marshall.
我知道你爱他
I know you do.
过来
Come here.
没事的
It's okay.
瞧...
Look...
婚姻是重大的事情
marriage is big.
你可以害怕
You're allowed to freak out.
但是为什么只有我害怕?
But why am I the only one?
为什么Marshall就没做什么疯狂的事?
How come Marshall isn't doing anything crazy?
那么我们只需要一只大纸箱
So all we need is one large shipping box
和100只白老鼠
and 100 white mice.
完成
All done.
Ted,我们去New Haven吧
Ted,let's go to New Haven.
Lily,\nLily,
别对你自己做这样的事
don't do this to yourself.
我只是想知道我能不能入围
I just need to know if I can get in.
如果我去面试
If I do this interview,
得到了这个项目
and get into the program,
到时我就能
then I'll know,
忘记这一切
and I can forget all about it,
去结婚
and get married.
来吧!
Come on!
这是场冒险
It's an adventure.
不，这不是冒险
No,it's not an adventure.
这是个错误
It's a mistake.
好吧，对，这是个错误
Okay,yes,it's a mistake.
我知道这是个错误
I know it's a mistake.
但生活中有些事情
But there are certain things in life
你知道会是错误
where you know it's a mistake
却又不明确一定是错误
but you don't really know it's a mistake
因为明确这是一个错误的唯一方法就是犯下这个错误
because the only way to really know it's\na mistake is to make the mistake,
然后再回头看，就可以说
and look back,and say,
"对，是个错误"
"yep.That was a mistake."
所以，不犯这个错误将是个更大的错误
So,really,the bigger mistake would be to not make the mistake,
因为这样你一辈子都不能肯定
because then you go your whole life\n not really knowing
这是不是错误
if something is a mistake or not.
而且，见鬼
And,damn it,
我从来没犯过错误!
I've made no mistakes!
我什么都完成了--
I've done all of this--
我的生活，爱情，事业--
my life,my relationship,my career--
零错误
mistake-free.
你觉得有道理吗?
Does any of this make sense to you?
我不知道,你说了很多次"错误"
I don't know.,You said "mistake" a lot.
Lily,别这么做
Lily,don't do this.
Ted,我两个月后就要结婚了
Ted,I'm getting married in two months,
我害怕
and I'm freaking out,
而你是我最好的朋友
and you're my best friend,
所以你必须原谅我这么做
and you just have to forgive me for this.
原谅你什么?
Forgive you for what?
Lily\nLily.
Lily!\nLily!
是Ted
this is Ted
被你留在路边的人
the guy you left stranded by the side of the road.
我只是想说祝你在面试中好运
I just wanted to say good luck with the interview,
记住带牛奶回来...
remember to pick up some milk...
而我回去的时候
and,when I get home,
要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
而且我也给了发了短信说了一样的话
And,also,I texted you the same thing.
我需要你帮个大忙
I need a big favor.
任何事都可以，兄弟
Anything,bro.
我要你来Duchess郡接我
I need you to come up to Duchess county\n and pick me up.
不
No.
事情紧急
It's kind of an emergency.
你在Duchess郡干吗?
What are you doing in Duchess county?
摘苹果
Apple picking.
你能过来吗?
Can you just get up here?
我希望我能帮你，兄弟
I wish I could help,buddy,
但是我工作没办法脱身
but I'm stuck here at work.
我们好像被陷住了
We're kind of swamped.
是Ted?
Is that Ted?
他被困在Duchess郡了
He's stuck in Duchess county.
你今晚不是有个重大的约会吗?
Don't you have a big date tonight?
Marshall.嗨
Marshall. Hi.
是的，是的
Yes. Yes,I do.
那你在Duchess郡干什么?
So what are you doing in Duchess county?
难道你兄弟来摘个苹果非得被拷问吗?tmd!
Can't a brother go apple picking without getting the third degree?Damn!
好吧，坚持
Okay,hang on.
我来接你
I'm coming to get you.
不!
No!
放松,伙计,我开Fiero去
Relax,man.I'll take the Fiero.
不 不 不
No,no,no.
只是...
Just...
算了
forget it.
开个玩笑
A little prank.
我不在Duchess郡
I'm not in Duchess county.
那么这是个玩笑?
So that's the prank?
你不在Duchess郡?
That you're not in Duchess county?
对
Yep.
你上当了!
Gotcha!
太经典了!
Classic!
我要挂了
Gotta go.
瞧这个
check out this one.
看起来确实像Butterfield
It actually looks like Butterfield.
你知道，远在国家科学研发公司
You know,over at the NRDC,
有一群真正忠诚的人们
it's a bunch of really committed people
他们的工作是非常严肃的拯救地球
who take their job of saving the\nearth very,very seriously.
那很棒
Which is great,
一切都是
and everything,
但我想在那可没有这么开心
but I can't imagine having this much\n fun over there.
你想来这做全职?
You thinking about coming to work here full-time?
也许
Maybe.
别告诉Lily,好吗?
Don't tell Lily,okay?
我要下班了
Taking off for the night.
谢谢,Tracy
Thanks,Tracy.
你们要在盒子上打洞吗?
Are you guys planning on punching\nsome holes in that box?
我们当然会
Of course we are.
你会这么想?
Were you going to think of that?
不
No.
已经很坏了
That would have been bad.
糟透了
Horrible.
幸运的是，我还可以打给一个人,让她载我回家
Luckily,there was still one person I\ncould call to get a ride home.
要搭车吗，牛仔?
Need a ride,cowboy?
对不起
Sorry.
我不进陌生人的车
I don't get in vans with strangers.
太遭了
too bad.
我有糖
I got candy.
糖?!
Candy?!
你不想告诉我你在Duchess郡
So you're not going to tell me what you were doing
的路边做什么?
by the side of a highway in Duchess county?
对
Nope.
发誓要保密的
Sworn to secrecy.
拜托
come on.
我喜欢你的帽子
I like your hat.
对
Right.
这让人难堪
This is embarrassing.
我把头发“加亮”了
I got Highlights.
在你的牙齿训练等候室?
for the waiting room of your dental practice?
“加亮”是本儿童杂志
Highlights is a children's magazine.
我听懂了
I got it.
我以为看起来会很酷
I thought it might look cool.
而帮我染发的人把“加亮”理解为
Of course my colorist took "Highlights" to mean,
"我想看起来像只老虎"
"I want to look like a tiger,"
所以我戴了帽子
hence the hat.
我一定要看看
I gotta see this.
不行
No way.
求你
Please.
我打赌看起来没那么遭
I bet it doesn't look that bad.
我打赌看起来棒极了!
I bet it looks grr-eat!
所以
So,
她说，改变话题
she says,changing the subject.
今晚有重大约会啊
Big date tonight.
她在Mosby的测试单上成绩如何?
How does she rate on the Mosby checklist?
有点太棒了
Kind of amazingly.
她和我一样28岁
she's 28,like me.
哇，我28岁了
I'm 28.
大学毕业-- 通过
college educated-- check.
打网球-- 通过
Plays tennis-- check.
最喜欢的书是“霍乱时期的爱情”-- 通过
favorite book is love in the time of cholera-- check.
我读过
I read that.
更像 "无打扰时期的爱情"
More like "love in the time of don't bothera."
你知道，我得说，在室内戴帽子
you know,it's very rude to wear a hat indoors.
是很不礼貌的
I'm just saying.
我们不在室内
We're not indoors.
我们在货车里
We're in a van.
货车有门--
Vans have doors--
让我看看你的头发
let me see your hair.
不给
Never.
还有什么?
What else?
她喜欢千层面
She loves lasagna.
呕吐
Barf.
你知道
You know,
我感觉到了一个图案
I am sensing a pattern here.
还有什么?
What else?
让我想想还有什么...
let's see what else...
她不喜欢看起来像老虎-- 通过
she doesn't look like a tiger-- check.
她想结婚生孩子吗?
And she's looking to get married and have kids?
通过 通过
Check and check.
她想要两个孩子--
She wants two kids--
一个男孩，一个女孩
a boy and a girl.
你知道，我一直在想这个
You know,I've been thinking about this.
我觉得我不想要孩子
I think I want to have zero kids.
真的吗? 你不想要孩子?
Really? You don't want kids?
你知道,Ted,
You know,Ted,
不是所有人都像你这么女人的
not everyone is as much of a woman as you.
我在开车
I'm driving.
瞧
look at that.
8:56.\n8:56.
我们来早了
You're early.
嘿，谢谢你接我
Hey,thanks for picking me up.
祝你约会好运
Good luck on your date.
我希望她就是你要找的
I hope she's everything you're looking for.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧，这一晚你显然过得不好
all right,you've clearly had a rough night.
我希望你进去的时候面带微笑，所以
I want you to go in there with a\nsmile on your face,so,
我要这么做
here's what I'm gonna do.
你要给我看你的头发?
You're gonna show me your hair?
事实上，我本来想让你看我的胸部...
Actually,I was gonna show you my breasts,but...
当然，也可以看头发
sure,we can do hair.
你让我的夜晚很愉快
you just made my night.
去吧
Go.
明天早上
Tomorrow morning,
Barney会送包裹
Barney's gonna send out the package,
Butterfield会被老鼠气死
and Butterfield's gonna be\nknee-deep in angry white mice.
伙计
dude.
嘿,伙计们
Hey,guys.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
Lil,你
So,Lil,did you,
买牛奶了吗?
get the milk?
我 我买了
I-I got it.
你觉得你想...
You think you might wanna...
喝牛奶吗?
drink the milk?
不
No.
不，我很好
Nope,I'm good.
我不需要牛奶
I don't need any milk.
瞧
Look,guys,
我知道牛奶很重要--
I know milk is important--
富含维他命A
it's got vitamin A,
维他命D
vitamin D,
喝牛奶是一天的好开始--
it's a great way to start the morning--
但Ted刚结束了一个重大约会
but Ted just had a huge date.
情况如何，伙计?
How'd it go,dude?
我没去
I didn't go.
什么?
What?
为什么?
Why?
我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
我不想见她
I don't want to meet her.
为什么?她听起来完美极了
Why? She sounds perfect.
我不想要完美
I don't want perfect.
我想要Robin
I want Robin.
天，又是这个
god,not this again.
Ted,这是个错误
Ted,it's a mistake.
也许
Maybe.
但这是我必须犯的错误
But it's a mistake I have to make.
错
Wrong.
这是你不必犯的错误
It's a mistake you don't have to make.
我有证据
Look at the evidence.
你和Robin试了一次又一次...
You and Robin have tried this again and again...
错误就是这么一回事
Here's the thing about mistakes.
有时，即使你知道是个错误
Sometimes,even when you know something's\n a mistake,
你还是要犯
you gotta make it anyway.
见鬼,好烫的盘子
sweet damn that's a hot plate.
嘿，牛奶坏了吗?
Hey,is this milk any good?
即使是非常非常蠢的错误
Even really,really dumb mistakes
老爸老妈罗曼史\n第一季 第二十一集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 01 Episode 21